Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
Fulton Lewis Jr. Papers
- Part I. News publications
  - Exclusive
    - Published material, 1963 Dec (Box 66)
    - Published material, 1964 Jan-Apr, Jun-Dec (Box 66)
    - Published material, 1965 Aug-Dec (Box 66)
    - Published material, 1966 Jan-Aug (Box 66)
    - Published material, 1957 Oct-Dec (Box 67)
    - Published material, 1958 Jan-Mar (Box 67)
  - Commentary
    - Published material, 1961 Oct (Box 67)
  - Buffalo Courier Express
    - Manuscripts, undated (Box 67)
- Part I. Other productions
  See also Part II, Manuscripts.
  - Television series
    - Scripts
      - Program 1, Harry Dexter White, 1954; final draft, typescript copy (Box 68)
      - Program 2, Guatemala, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 3, Civil Service, 1954; final draft, typescript copy (Box 68)
      - Program 4, Special Weapons, 1954; final draft, typescript copy (Box 68)
      - Program 5, Manpower & Defense, 1954; final draft, carbon copy (Box 68)
      - Program 6, The Institute of the Pacific, 1954; final draft, carbon copy (Box 68)
      - Program 8, The Coffee Situation, 1954; final draft, carbon copy (Box 68)
      - Program 12, Puerto Rico, 1954; notes and final draft, holograph, typescript and carbon copies (Box 68)
      - Program 13, Brainwashing-Part I, 1954; Notes and final draft, holograph typescript, and carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 14, Brainwashing-Part II, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 15, The Lie Detector, 1954; final draft, typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 16, Senatorial Elections, 1954; final draft, typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 17, Federal Housing Agency, 1954; final draft, typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 18, Background of the McCarthy-Army Hearings, 1954; final draft, typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 19, McCarthy-Stevens Wrangle, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 20, Personalities in the Hearings, 1954; final draft, lightly revised, typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 21, Central America, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 22, The President and the Democrats, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Not numbered, Investigation of Investigations, 1954; final draft, carbon (Box 68)
      - Not numbered, Tennessee Valley Authority, 1954; final draft, typescript (Box 68)
      - Not numbered, Western European Union, 1954; draft, lightly revised typescript and carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 1, Formosa, Land Reform, 1955; draft, heavily revised typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 3, Quemoy Island, 1955; draft, heavily revised typescript (Box 68)
      - Program 5, Continental Defense, 1955; draft, work sheets, holograph, typescript and carbon (Box 68)
      - Program 6, General George E. Stratemeyer, 1955; draft, heavily revised typescript, and carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 9, Argonne, 1955; draft, typescript and carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 10, France, The Problem Child, 1955; final draft, typescript and carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 11, Spain, 1955; notes and final draft, holograph, heavily revised typescript and carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 13, Interview with Major General Claire Chennault, 1955; draft, lightly revised, typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 14, German Recovery, 1955; notes and draft, heavily revised carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 15, FBI, 1955; draft, heavily revised typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 16, FBI Training, 1955; draft, typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 17, Junior Achievement, 1955; draft, lightly revised typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 18, Air Force Academy, 1955; draft, lightly revised typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 19, Heart Diseases, 1955; draft, lightly revised carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 20, Idlewild International Airport in NY, 1955; draft, lightly revised typescript and carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 21, This Small World, 1955; draft, typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 22 & 23, Narcotics, 1955; final draft, lightly revised carbon (Box 69)
      - Program 24 & 25, Guatemala, 1955; draft, heavily revised typescript (Box 69)
      - Program 26, Inter-American Highway, 1955; draft, typescript and lightly revised carbon (Box 69)
    - Subject arrangement
      - Advertisement for TV Program, "War of Worlds" (Box 69)
      - Biography of Edgar Faure, President of Council of Ministers, France, 1955 (Box 69)
      - Correspondence, Apr, Sept, 1954; undated (Box 69)
      - Lists: Commissionable Price List, 1953 (Box 69)
      - Lists of TV Stations, 1954 (Box 69)
      - Publicity, 1946; 1954-1955 (Box 69)
  - Articles, manuscript
    - America at War, undated (Box 70)
    - America's Town Meeting of the Air, 1946 (Box 70)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, 1944 (Box 70)
    - The Communist Nature of the American Civil Liberties Union, undated (Box 70)
    - Cordell Hull; Errand Boy, 1935 (Box 70)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution Congress, 1962 (Box 70)
    - Democracy with a Gun in its Ribs (Box 70)
    - The Knicker-Bocker Disaster, undated; 1955 (Box 70)
    - Memorandum re Germany, 1955 (Box 70)
    - "On This Side of the Iron Curtain, Who are Our Friends and Who are Our Enemies?", 1955 (Box 70)
    - The Paradox of Reciprocal Tariff Agreements, undated (Box 70)
    - The Psaltre Sermon, undated (Box 70)
    - Three Hundred Years of Tradition, undated (Box 70)
    - Untitled, Annual Meeting of Stockholders, 1954 (Box 70)
    - Untitled, re atomic energy, undated (Box 70)
    - Untitled, re Battle of Gettysburg (Box 70)
    - Untitled, re politicians, 1962 (Box 70)
    - Untitled, re the 75th Congress, undated; session ran from 1937-1939 (Box 70)
  - Articles, published
    - "A Gatt in Your Ribs", 1956 (Box 70)
    - Can Beryllium Break the Bottleneck?, undated (Box 70)
    - Has the Youth Congress Washed Itself Out?, 1940 (Box 70)
    - How the Republicans Hope to Beat Roosevelt, 1936 (Box 70)
  - Book
    - Untitled book about co-operatives, 1948; manuscript (Box 71)
  - Dramatic sketches
    - "Heroism", undated; manuscript (Box 71)
  - Interviews
    - President Chiang Kai-Shek, 1954; manuscript (Box 71)
    - Admiral Sir John Edelsten, 1953; manuscript (Box 71)
    - Joe Smith, undated; manuscript (Box 71)
  - Plays
    - Untitled manuscripts, undated (Box 71)
    - Untitled, incomplete manuscripts (Box 71)
  - Poems, manuscripts
    - Doug's Communiqué, undated (Box 72)
    - Halloween Motif, undated (Box 72)
    - The W.S.S. Campaign, undated (Box 72)
  - Short stories
    - "A Picture", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "The Beggar Who Rode", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "The Final Curtain", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "Fog", manuscript (Box 72)
    - "God of the Ups and Downs", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "His Wife", 1923; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "Never-Come-Back Island", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "The Patriarch", undated; incomplete manuscript (Box 72)
    - "Pay It With Flowers", undated; incomplete manuscript (Box 72)
    - "Pharaoh's Army Gits Drowned", undated; manuscript (Box 72)
    - "So This is Jail", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "Stowaway", undated; incomplete manuscript (Box 73)
    - "The Once", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "This is the Way the Ladies Ride", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "Two for the Money", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "Two Men Find Each Other", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "The Walled Garden", 1932; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "The Wooden Indian", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - "The Young Man of the Mountains", undated; manuscript (Box 73)
    - Untitled manuscript, undated (Box 73)
    - Fragments, unidentifiable, undated (Box 73)
    - Fragments, unidentifiable, undated (Box 74)
  - By others
    - Articles about Lewis, published (Box 74)
    - C, 1938-1965 (Box 74)
    - K-O, 1940-1966 (Box 74)
    - T-W, 1940-1954 (Box 74)
    - Author unknown, no title, undated (Box 74)
    - Book, An American With Guts, by Edward Edell, undated; galley proof (Box 74)
- Part I. Reference files
  This series is subdivided as follows: (1) General files, (2) Fund for the Republic, (3) General Agreements on Tariff and Trade (GATT), (4) Radio Free Europe, (5) Office of Price Administration, and (6) Co-operatives.
  See also Part II, Reference files.
  - General files
    - Abolition clippings, 1961 (Box 75)
    - American College of Radio Reporters, 1944 (Box 75)
    - American Medical Association, 1965 (Box 75)
    - AMA Medicare, 1965; 1964-1965 (Box 75)
    - American Mercury, 1947 (Box 75)
    - American Speakers & Writers Bureau, Inc., 1946 (Box 75)
    - America's Town Meeting of the Air, 1946 (Box 75)
    - America Writer's Association, 1946 (Box 75)
    - Anti-Semitic, 1951-1960 (Box 75)
    - Appropriations, 1947 (Box 75)
    - Articles, 1942-1946 (Box 76)
    - Balsam, Louis, 1941-1944 (Box 76)
    - Balsam, Louis vs. Fulton Lewis, Jr., 1944 Jan (Box 76)
    - Benton, William, 1947 (Box 76)
    - [John] Birch Society, 1959; Sept 15, 1961 (Box 76)
    - Baker, Bobby, 1965 (Box 76)
    - Braceros (Farm Labor), 1962-1965 (Box 76)
    - Brand's, 1964 (Box 77)
    - Bricker, Governor John, 1944 (Box 77)
    - Bridges, Senator, 1961; comments, clippings (Box 77)
    - Broadcasts (not made), 1959 (Box 77)
    - Bunche, Dr. Ralph, 1962 (Box 77)
    - Bundy, Edgar C., 1958-1960 (Box 77)
    - Business, Letter, Congressional, 1948, Jun (Box 77)
    - Campaigns, 1960 (Box 77)
    - Choir, 1948 (Box 77)
    - Column ideas, undated (Box 77)
    - Civil rights, 1964; 1965-1966 (Box 77)
    - Coal, 1946 (Box 77)
    - Communism, 1946-1947 (Box 77)
    - Condolence, 1948 (Box 77)
    - Congressional Material, 1947-1948 (Box 78)
    - Connally Amendment, 1945; 1960 (Box 78)
    - Contests, 1947 (Box 78)
    - Copper, 1946-1948 (Box 78)
    - Cuba, 1963-1967; 1960-1961 (Box 78)
    - Dahlberg, Reverend Edwin, 1943; 1958 (Box 78)
    - Dean, Mervell M., 1947 (Box 78)
    - Democratic National Convention, undated (Box 78)
    - Dewey, Governor Thomas E., 1948; 1943-1944 (Box 78)
    - Dolph, W.B., 1941-1947 (Box 78)
    - DuPont Award, 1942-1948 (Box 78)
    - Eaton, Cyrus, 1961 (Box 79)
    - Economics, 1947 (Box 79)
    - Edwards, William J., 1946 (Box 79)
    - Election Material, 1944 (Box 79)
    - Ensign, Madeline (Carol Story), 1945 (Box 79)
    - Fact, 1965 (Box 79)
    - FBI, 1949 (Box 79)
    - Foreign Aid, 1964 (Box 79)
    - Foreign Aid, Russian, 1965 (Box 79)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1963-1964 (Box 79)
    - Freedom Academy, 1959-1960 (Box 79)
    - Granik, Theodore, undated (Box 79)
    - Greek Junket, 1961 (Box 79)
    - Goldwater, 1963; 1964 (Box 80)
    - Goldwater-Miller Support, 1964 (Box 80)
    - "Guideposts", 1950 (Box 80)
    - Hillman, Sidney, 1942 (Box 80)
    - Hillman, Sidney & Communist Political Assoc., 1944 (Box 80)
    - Honolulu, 1942-1946; undated (Box 80)
    - Homosexuals, 1965 (Box 81)
    - House of Un-American Activities, 1959-1960 (Box 81)
    - Horses, 1947 (Box 81)
    - Housing, 1946; 1947,; 1955 (Box 81)
    - Hungarian Delegation, 1957 (Box 81)
    - Hungary, 1965 (Box 81)
    - Imports, 1962 (Box 81)
    - Indians, 1961 (Box 81)
    - "In Fact", 1947 (Box 81)
    - International Council of Christian Churches, 1960 (Box 82)
    - Jenkins, Walter, 1964 (Box 82)
    - Johnson, 1964; speeches (Box 82)
    - Jordon, Major, 1949; 1950 (Box 82)
    - Kempton, James Murray, 1958 (Box 82)
    - Kornitzer, Bela, 1960 (Box 82)
    - Labor, 1947 (Box 82)
    - Landrum, 1960 (Box 82)
    - Latin America, 1960 (Box 82)
    - Legal cases, undated (Box 82)
    - Legal proceedings, 1946; 1947 (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Fulton Jr., 1962 (Box 82)
    - Lewis Machine Tool Co., undated (Box 82)
    - Lewis, Fulton Jr.
      - Notes, 1964; 1965,; undated (Box 82)
      - Notes re tour in East Berlin, undated (Box 82)
      - Fulton Lewis Jr. for President Club, 1947-1949 (Box 82)
    - Look Magazine, 1947 (Box 83)
    - Lumber, 1946 (Box 83)
    - Lustron-Tucker Co. Housing, 1946 (Box 83)
    - Mail & misc., 1940; 1942,; 1945 (Box 83)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (General), 1952; 1964 (Box 83)
    - McCarthy, undated (Box 83)
    - McIntire, Dr., 1966 (Box 83)
    - Meat, 1945; 1946,; 1964 (Box 84)
    - Medicare, 1965 (Box 84)
    - Minnesota Shakedown, 1944 (Box 84)
    - Minuteman, undated (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous, 1942; 1945,; 1947 (Box 84)
    - Morris, George, 1959 (Box 84)
    - Movies, 1947 (Box 84)
    - Music, undated (Box 84)
    - National Council of Churches, 1961; 1965 (Box 84)
    - National Council of Churches, 1966 (Box 85)
    - National Council of Churches, 1960-1961 (Box 85)
    - National Council of Churches, 1946-1960 (Box 85)
    - National Council of Churches, 1960-1965 (Box 86)
    - National Council of Churches, 1960 (Box 87)
    - Navy Plan for National Security, 1946 (Box 87)
    - Newspaper clippings and editorials, 1945 (Box 87)
    - Mme Ngo Dinh Nhu, 1964 (Box 87)
    - Oakland, Inc., 1944 (Box 87)
    - Oceanography, 1965 (Box 87)
    - O'dell, 1963 (Box 87)
    - Office, 1940 (Box 87)
    - Office correspondence, 1945; 1946,; 1948 (Box 87)
    - Office supplies, 1947 (Box 87)
    - Operation Abolition, 1960; 1961 (Box 87)
    - Operation Abolition, 1961 (Box 88)
    - Opocensky, Milan, 1958; 1964 (Box 88)
    - Oppenheimer, 1954; 1955,; 1956 (Box 88)
    - Organs, 1948; 1950,; 1952 (Box 88)
    - Organs, 1949-1957; 1948-1959 (Box 89)
    - Orr, Ella, undated (Box 89)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1954-1959 (Box 89)
    - Paid bills, 1948 (Box 89)
    - Panama Canal, 1963-1965 (Box 89)
    - Pan American Highway, 1945 (Box 89)
    - Pan American Highway, 1945-1946 (Box 90)
    - Peace, 1962-1964 (Box 90)
    - Pearl Harbor Investigation, 1940-1945 (Box 90)
    - Pearl Harbor Investigation, 1941-1947 (Box 91)
    - Personal records, 1946 (Box 91)
    - Placid Harbor, 1944; 1945 (Box 91)
    - Placid Harbor, 1946 (Box 92)
    - Police Terror in the US, 1950 (Box 92)
    - Political Action Committee, 1944 (Box 92)
    - Possibilities Unlimited, 1946 (Box 92)
    - Postmaster General, 1930 (Box 92)
    - Prayer, The Lord's (teenage version), 1957-1961 (Box 92)
    - Prayers, 1962-1967 (Box 92)
    - Presidential Disability, 1957 (Box 92)
    - Radio Correspondents' Association, 1939-1945 (Box 93)
    - Ratings, 1956 (Box 93)
    - Right to Work, 1965; 1966 (Box 93)
    - Right to Work, 1966 (Box 94)
    - Roberts, Holland De Witt, 1959 (Box 94)
    - Roberts, Arch E. Major, 1962 (Box 94)
    - Rohl, Wyman, Carol, undated (Box 94)
    - Roosevelt, Elliott, 1946 (Box 94)
    - Rural Electrification Act, 1955-1957 (Box 94)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1961 (Box 94)
    - Saturday Evening Post, 1947 (Box 94)
    - Southern Senatorial Candidates, 1962 (Box 94)
    - Selma, Alabama, Rep. William L. Dickinson, 1965 (Box 94)
    - Smith, Anti-strike Bill, 1947 (Box 94)
    - Spofford, Rev. William B., undated (Box 94)
    - Stamps, 1946; 1948 (Box 94)
    - Sugar, 1946; 1947 (Box 94)
    - Sugar, 1946 (Box 95)
    - Sussman, Lelia, 1945 (Box 95)
    - Synthetic rubber, 1942 (Box 95)
    - Textiles, 1960 (Box 95)
    - Transcriptions, 1947 (Box 95)
    - Teletypes, undated (Box 96)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1949 (Box 96)
    - Three Little Swiss Guys, 1947 (Box 96)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1947 (Box 96)
    - Un-American Activities Committee, 1959 (Box 96)
    - Veterans Training and Unemployment Compensation (Box 96)
    - Vietnam, 1963-1965 (Box 96)
    - Wallace, Henry Agard, 1945 (Box 96)
    - Wallace, Mike, 1958, Feb; interview (Box 96)
    - White Radio Bill, 1947 (Box 96)
    - Winchell, Walter, 1947 (Box 96)
    - Wol, "the voice of Washington", 1947 (Box 96)
    - Wheat, 1964 (Box 96)
    - Wooden Church Crusader, 1954; 1956 (Box 96)
    - Wyzaski, Judge, 1961 (Box 97)
    - Week News clippings, undated (Box 97)
  - Fund for the Republic
    - General, 1953-1961; clippings, correspondence, pamphlets (Box 97)
    - Academic Freedom, 1956 (Box 98)
    - American Heritage, 1955 (Box 98)
    - American Legion, 1955 (Box 98)
    - Awards and grants, 1955; 1956 (Box 98)
    - Bibliography, 1952; 1953,; 1955 (Box 98)
    - Black listing, 1956 (Box 98)
    - Congressional Investigation, 1955 (Box 98)
    - Council for Social Action, 1955; 1956 (Box 99)
    - Film Project, 1956 (Box 99)
    - Ford, Henry II, 1955 (Box 99)
    - Ford Foundation
      - General, 1954; 1955,; 1963 (Box 99)
      - Reports, 1953; 1955,; 1958 (Box 100)
    - Great Books, 1955; 1956 (Box 100)
    - Hallock, Hoffman, 1953-1956 (Box 100)
    - Herblock, 1955 (Box 100)
    - Hoffman, Paul G.
      - Correspondence, 1955; 1956 (Box 100)
      - Clippings, 1952; 1956 (Box 101)
      - Books, magazines, press releases, 1951; 1955,; 1956 (Box 101)
    - Hutchis, Robert M., 1959 (Box 101)
    - Jury tapping, 1955 (Box 101)
    - Millis, Walter, 1955 (Box 101)
    - Other foundations, 1953-1955 (Box 101)
    - Racial Equality, 1955-1956 (Box 101)
    - Reece Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 101)
    - Richard Rovere, 1956 (Box 101)
    - Rossiter, Clinton, 1955; 1956 (Box 101)
    - Security, 1955 (Box 102)
    - Southern Methodist University, 1955 (Box 102)
    - Stanford University, 1955 (Box 102)
    - The Tablet, 1955 (Box 102)
    - Talking Books Project, 1956 (Box 102)
    - UNESCO, 1955 (Box 102)
    - World Federalists, 1954 (Box 102)
  - General Agreements on Tariff and Trade (GATT)
    - General
      - Books, clippings, 1955; 1956,; 1958 (Box 102)
      - Government publications, 1954-1958 (Box 103)
      - Manuscripts, mimeographed material, pamphlets, photostats, 1955-1958 (Box 103)
    - Agriculture, 1958 (Box 104)
    - Airplanes, 1958 (Box 104)
    - Boats, 1956 (Box 104)
    - Binoculars, Cameras, 1956 (Box 104)
    - Ceramics, Glassware, 1956; 1957,; 1958 (Box 104)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1956; 1957 (Box 104)
    - Cigarette lighters, 1956 (Box 104)
    - Clothing, 1956 (Box 104)
    - Electrical Equipment, 1957 (Box 104)
    - Factories closing, 1956; 1958 (Box 104)
    - Flowers, 1956 (Box 104)
    - Foods
      - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 104)
      - Published material, 1956-1958 (Box 105)
    - Furniture, 1956 (Box 105)
    - Household goods, 1957 (Box 105)
    - International Trade Organization, 1956 (Box 105)
    - Labor, 1956-1958 (Box 105)
    - Laos, 1956-1959 (Box 105)
    - League of Women Voters, 1955-1956 (Box 105)
    - Leather, 1957 (Box 105)
    - Linen, 1956 (Box 105)
    - Liquor, 1958 (Box 106)
    - Machinery & motors, 1956 (Box 106)
    - Metals, 1956-1958 (Box 106)
    - Musical Instruments, 1958 (Box 106)
    - Nails, 1954 (Box 106)
    - Oil, 1956-1958 (Box 106)
    - Paid Mass Orders, 1956 (Box 106)
    - Reciprocal Trade Act Renewal, 1958 (Box 106)
    - Roller Bearings, 1957 (Box 106)
    - Rope, 1954 (Box 107)
    - Textiles
      - Correspondence. & reports, 1956-1958 (Box 107)
      - Published material, 1955-1957 (Box 107)
    - Thermometers, 1956 (Box 107)
    - Time pieces, 1956-1958 (Box 107)
    - Tobacco, 1956 (Box 107)
    - Umbrellas, 1954 (Box 107)
    - Wood, 1956-1958 (Box 107)
    - Wool, 1956 (Box 107)
  - Radio Free Europe
    - Advertising Council, 1958 (Box 108)
    - American Legion, 1958 (Box 108)
    - American Telephone & Telegraph Co. [AT&T], 1958 (Box 108)
    - Anonymous letters, 1958 (Box 108)
    - Assembly of Captive European Nations, 1958 (Box 108)
    - Atlantic Refining Co., 1958 (Box 108)
    - Bartholomew Case, 1958 (Box 108)
    - Brada, George, 1958 (Box 108)
    - Chrysler Co., 1958 (Box 109)
    - Clardy, Kit, 1955; 1958 (Box 109)
    - Congressional Investigation request, 1958 (Box 109)
    - Corporations & stockholders, 1958 (Box 109)
    - Crusade for Freedom
      - Correspondence about, 1957; 1958 (Box 109)
      - Correspondence from, clippings, 1957; 1958 (Box 110)
      - Published material, 1957; 1958 (Box 111)
      - Radio advertising, 1958 (Box 111)
    - Czechoslovakia (from Mr. Sisa), 1951-1958 (Box 111)
    - Defectors, 1957; 1958 (Box 112)
    - East Europe (magazines), 1957; 1958 (Box 112)
    - Ex Employees, 1958 (Box 112)
    - Facts Forum, 1956 (Box 112)
    - General, undated (Box 112)
    - General Motors Corp., 1950 (Box 113)
    - Heinlich, Bill, 1957 (Box 113)
    - Hungary, 1956-1957 (Box 113)
    - Investigation, 1957 (Box 113)
    - Liberation Committees, 1958 (Box 113)
    - London Polish Daily, 1958 (Box 113)
    - Mikees, Dr. Joseph, 1957 (Box 113)
    - Mss. and Notes, 1953; 1957,; 1958 (Box 113)
    - Monsanto Chemical Co., 1958 (Box 113)
    - New York Daily Guidance (photostats), 1957 (Box 113)
    - Otto at Austria, 1957; 1958 (Box 113)
    - Peters, Dr. Bislav, 1957 (Box 113)
    - Poland, 1952; 1954,; 1958 (Box 114)
    - Readers Digest, 1958 (Box 114)
    - Roumania, 1958 (Box 114)
    - Sisa, Stephen, 1957; 1958 (Box 114)
    - Socony Mobil Oil Co., 1958 (Box 114)
    - Standard Oil Co. at New Jersey, 1958 (Box 114)
    - State Department, 1958 (Box 114)
    - Sworn statements of F. Lewis Jr. Exhibits, 1958 (Box 114)
    - The Texas Company, 1958 (Box 114)
    - United States Government, 1958 (Box 114)
    - Washington Report Column, 1957 (Box 114)
    - Westinghouse Corporation, 1958 (Box 114)
    - Withycomb, Donald, 1951; 1952 (Box 114)
  - Office of Price Administration
    - Automobiles, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Cattle, 1944 (Box 115)
    - Chester Bowles-Paul Porter, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Congressional Mail, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Cost of Living, undated (Box 115)
    - Cotton, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Dairy Products, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Dry Goods, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Food, 1946 (Box 115)
    - Gasoline (Wichata Case) (Box 115)
    - General-OPA (Office of Price Administration) (Box 115)
    - General-OPA (Office of Price Administration) (Box 116)
    - Hides, 1946 (Box 116)
    - Letters praising Fulton Lewis Jr., 1946 (Box 116)
    - Letters in favor, 1946 (Box 116)
    - Livingston, John C., undated; interview or broadcast (Box 116)
    - Lumber, 1946 (Box 116)
    - Meat, 1946 (Box 116)
    - Mail results, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Metals, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Misc. cases, 1946 (Box 117)
    - National Association of Manufacturers, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Personnel, 1945 (Box 117)
    - Propaganda, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Petroleum, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Rent, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Schy, Sigmund, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Steel, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Sugar, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Textiles, 1946 (Box 117)
    - Thorsen, Wallace, 1946 (Box 117)
    - The Three Little Swiss, 1946 (Box 118)
  - Co-operatives
    - Correspondence, 1947; 1948 (Box 119)
    - Cases in relation to Farmers' Cooperative Association, 1947 (Box 119)
    - Comments & citations on broadcasts of F. Lewis, 1947 (Box 119)
    - Clippings, published material (Box 119)
    - Correspondence, published material, 1947 (Box 120)
    - Clippings, published material, 1947 (Box 120)
    - General, 1944-1948 (Box 121)
    - General, 1946-1948 (Box 122)
- Part I. Personal file
  - News clippings about Lewis
    - [General], 1920-1948 (Box 123)
    - [General], 1949, Jan-Dec (Box 124)
    - [General], 1949, Dec (Box 125)
    - [General], 1949 (Box 126)
    - [General], 1950, Jan-Feb (Box 127)
    - [General], 1950, Apr, Aug-Nov; 1951 (Box 128)
    - [General], 1951, Feb, Mar, May, Jun (Box 129)
    - [General], 1951, Jul-1952, Apr (Box 130)
    - [General], 1952, May-Dec (Box 131)
    - [General], 1953 (Box 132)
    - [General], 1953, Aug-Nov; 1954 (Box 133)
    - [General], 1955-1963; 1965-1966 (Box 134)
    - [General], 1966 (Box 135)
    - [General], Undated (Box 135)
    - Lewis Indictment (Box 135)
    - McCarthy-Lewis, 1954 (Box 135)
    - McCarthy-Lewis, 1954 (Box 136)
  - Clippings, unarranged (Box 137)
  - Business records
    - Expense accounts, 1943-1947 (Box 138)
    - Insurance, legal, 1948 (Box 138)
  - Itinerary, 1944-1947; 1949 (Box 139)
  - Lectures and trips
    - Overseas trip, 1945 (Box 139)
    - Outline for lecture series, 1960 (Box 139)